♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
——·旗木译制·——
我觉得这事儿你没想清楚
I don't think you've thought this through.
到了机场遇见人质劫持怎么办?
What do you do with the hostages when you get to the airport?
让他们跟我来呗
They're coming with me.
可以考虑飞机派对
We're talking party plane.
一路嗨飞利比亚
All the way to Libya.
Rita 真是太棒了 好为你们高兴啊
Rita, that's so wonderful. I'm so happy for you!
你和Erin你们俩
You and Erin both.
你要不自己遛弯儿吧
Ah, you'd better take a hike.
干嘛?
Why?
我妈跟我Rita姨打电话呢
My mom's talking to my Aunt Rita.
气氛不会很开心
This isn't going to be pretty.
了解 回见好吧?
Gotcha. Later, huh?
情况有待观察
That remains to be seen.
太难以置信了 小Erin都要结婚了
I can't believe it. Little Erin getting married.
她应该没有被逼婚 但愿吧
She's not rushing into this, I hope.
没没 怎么会了啦 二十一岁...
Oh, no, no, of course not. Twenty-one is...
我哪里阴阳怪气了 真是的 Rita
I'm not implying anything, for goodness sake, Rita.
我只是... 太兴奋了嘛 哪里?
I'm just... this is so exciting! Where?
好的呀
That sounds lovely.
我猜老妈给你掏这笔钱? 不 不...
I presume Mom's footing the bill? No, no...
你Erin表姐要结婚了
Your cousin Erin is getting married.
我听出来了
So I gathered.
可得花上一大笔银子啊
You know there'll be hell to pay.
大家伙应该都听到这个好消息了吧
Well, I guess you all heard the wonderful news.
小Erin要结婚了
Little Erin is getting married.
在利威尔的温莎山度假村
At the Windsor Hills Resort in Leeville.
我去 这可得烧Rita不少银子喔
Whoa-ho! That'll set Rita back a pretty penny.
毛哇 我妈掏
Not Rita. Mother.
铁公鸡为了她最好闺女的宝贝孩子 情愿拔光毛
Nothing but the best for her favorite daughter's darling offspring.
温莎山
Windsor Hills.
那儿可有大名鼎鼎的十三球洞诶
They've got that legendary thirteenth hole!
行了 Jake 是婚礼 别想高尔夫
Forget it, Jake. No golf. Wedding.
我已经开始遗憾参加不了婚礼了
I'm almost sorry I'm going to miss this.
正相反 宝贝儿
On the contrary, sweetie:
你和Quinn要去当伴娘
you and Quinn are going to be bridesmaids.
这事一万个准
I made sure of that.
伴娘?
Bridesmaids?
要是裙子颜色不搭 我能染头发嘛?
Can I dye my hair if the dress doesn't match?
真是天意弄人啊 我 居然要做伴娘
What a hideous twist of fate. Me, a bridesmaid.
哎呦没那么糟啦 我知道 没错
Aw, it won't be that bad, I mean, sure,
你得穿那种桃色花边裙
you'll have to wear some frilly peach-color dress
变成马戏团怪人那种样子
that makes you look like a circus freak,
还会被爱不释手的怪蜀黍捏脸
and you'll be pinched by incontinent old uncles
以为你现在还只有六岁 还会...
who still think you're still six years old, and...
到咯
Here we are.
抱歉 本店只提供婚礼服务 不做葬礼
I'm sorry, we only do weddings, not funerals.
不骗你 我爱葬礼更胜一筹
Believe me, I'd prefer a funeral.
亲爱的 不想结婚可以不结的
Dearie, you don't have to get married if you don't want to...
难道你想?
or do you?
我是Chambers先生和Danielson小姐的伴娘
I'm a bridesmaid in the Chambers-Danielson wedding.
有了
Here it is.
遗憾 这款裙子超级萌人
Pity. They're such lovely dresses.
老天爷没怎么生给你一副翘臀
Nature didn't see fit to give you much in the way of hips,
是不是 亲爱的?
did she, dearie?
我感觉有点不舒服
I think I'm going to be ill.
你不会介意的吧?
Is that a problem for you?
转身过来吧
Turn around, please.
Scarlet 到那天你会变得更可人
Oh, Scarlet, you grow lovelier by the day!
我会杀了你 再用这条裙子盖上你
I will kill you, and bury your body in this dress.
Daria?
你在这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
显而易见啊
Isn't is obvious?
镇上阿拉伯酋长级土豪又买了几个老婆
An Arab sheik's in town to buy a few more wives.
体育馆有一场婚博会 我们是模特
They're putting on a bridal expo in the gym. We're modeling!
婚博会?
A bridal expo?
真是会给高中小孩灌药啊
That's a good message to send to high school students.
是一场为课外活动集资的活动
It's a fundraiser for extracurricular activities.
我在捉摸什么样的课余活动
I wonder what kind of extracurricular activities
会引发婚礼...
would lead to a wedding...
你呢? 要演话剧还是什么吗?
What about you? Are you in a play or something?
是 我要演林肯夫人 演疯了以后的她
Yes. I'm playing Mrs. Lincoln, after she went crazy.
我没听说过她疯了耶
I didn't know she went crazy.
有的 所以林肯才会饮弹自尽嘛
Oh, yeah. That's why Lincoln shot himself.
走啦 Brittany
Come on, Brittany.
我们去试完装
Let's finish out fitting,
我会跟你讲林肯到底是怎么死掉的
and I'll tell you all about how nice Mr. Lincoln really died.
难道子弹没把他打死吗?
You mean the bullet didn't kill him?
别动
Hold still.
你这身板儿可给我加了不少苦活儿呢
I'm having a hard enough time with your body as it is.
好吧 全程羞辱到此画上圆满句号
Well, I think my humiliation is complete now.
真很搭我头发诶
It does match my hair!
我那话说早了
I spoke too soon.
搞不懂你干嘛不让人家带高尔夫球杆
I don't know why you didn't let me bring my golf clubs.
Jake 我们来看我家人 不是来玩好吧
Jake, we're here to see my family, not to have fun.
这次陪你妹妹的又是那个男人?
Who's escorting your sister to this, anyway?
她甩了那个雕刻家
Well, she dumped the sculptor,
后来的跳伞教练也遭遇意外身亡了
the skydiving instructor had that horrible accident,
我估计那个Bruno就是临时葬礼陪衬
and I believe that Bruno is in some federal facility.
所以我也不造诶...
So I don't know...
你们家Rita还真是选郎有方
That Rita sure knows how to pick 'em.
谋杀啊 谋杀啊
Redrum! Redrum!
语出惊悚片《闪灵》指酒店谋杀
你老妈这次可要下血本了
This will cost your mother a fortune!
不然她也没处花她的票子了
Well, what else should she spend her money on?
难道要无聊到给她其他外甥女也交点教育基金嘛?
Something boring, like college funds for her other granddaughters?
全当给自己解心宽
I just keep telling myself
就当Erin没咱家俩宝出身好吧
that Erin hasn't had the advantages our girls have.
出身好?
Advantages?
我也纳闷
You got me.
你知道 被妹子们看见 我们就死定了
You know, if the girls see us, we're going to die.
她们说 我们在场 她们会难为情的
They said we'd make them feel self-conscious.
开玩笑吧? 她们想让我们来啦 哥们
Are you kidding? They want us to come, bro.
妹子想时 嘴上会说不要
That's why they told us not to.
她们会觉得如果真邀请我们来婚博会
They knew that if they invited us to a bridal expo,
那我们根本不会鸟她们的茬儿
there's no way we'd go near the place.
那我们来干嘛的?
Then why are we here?
偷尝禁果啊 老兄 禁果啊
Forbidden fruit, man. Forbidden fruit.
你说话的时候 真心觉得自己过脑了么?
When you hear yourself talk, does it make sense to you?
偶尔咯
Sometimes.
嘿 小伙
Hey, fellas.
提醒二位一下 我们很欢迎同性伴侣的
Just want you to know, we welcome same-sex partners.
要不要买戒指 你们自己看
What you do with the ring is your business.
这车可不便宜 开的时候当心点
This is an expensive vehicle. Be careful with it.
行啊
Yeah, right.
Helen
Helen!
Rita
Rita!
还好吗 Jake?
How are you, Jake?
也还不赖啦...
Well, I'm not bad...
姑娘们真是可爱
Oh, the girls look lovely.
可Daria
But Daria,
你怎么没穿其他伴娘的那套礼服啊?
why didn't you get the same dress as the other bridesmaids?
穿了
I did.
没参加彩排晚宴真是抱歉 Rita
I'm sorry about the rehearsal dinner, Rita.
昨天下午我开会开个没完
I had meetings all yesterday afternoon,
等我们要上路的时候...
and by the time we got on the road...
大伙 这是Paul 我男朋友
Everyone, this is Paul, my beau.
好啊
Hello.
Paul Meyerson?
Jake? Jake和我是一个童子军团的
Jake? Jake and I were in Boy Scouts together.
带球杆了没?
You bring your clubs?
爸 你刚在车上说谁选郎有方来着?
Dad, what was that you said about knowing how to pick 'em?
Daria...
Oh, Daria...
哇 那是谁啊?
Wow, who's that?
Amy姨?
Aunt Amy?
刮车了没事
I don't mind a few dents,
但要是敢换电台 你就死定了
but change the radio station and you're a dead man.
Amy 好开心啊
Amy, how delightful.
还以为你不来了呢
I thought you weren't coming.
本来没想
I wasn't,
不过想想你俩都能尽弃前嫌 我的话...
but I thought if you two could put aside years of
bitterness and resentment, then so can I...
一天也无妨
for a day.
Amy 看你在胡说八道什么了啦?
Oh, Amy, why do you say such ridiculous things?
你指说出口吗? Jake 还跟Helen过呢?
Out loud? So, Jake. You're still with Helen, huh?
不屈不挠 精神可嘉
Shows remarkable fortitude.
Roger 跳伞事业怎么样了?
And Roger. How's the skydiving going?
Amy Roger过世了 这位是Paul
Amy, Roger passed away. This is Paul.
抱歉 Paul 你好啊
Oh, sorry. Paul, how do you do?
Roger谁啊?
Who's Roger?
他跳伞降落撞到牛
He fell onto a cow.
真是千千万之中的幸运儿
And he was one of the lucky ones.
孩子们
Girls.
嘿 不挖点槽点出来
Hey, what's the point of a senseless tragedy
无聊悲剧又意义何在呢?
if you can't find a little humor in it?
你的脑洞我喜欢 Daria
I like the way you think, Daria.
那个 Amy 我还没给你安排好座位呢...
Now, Amy, I'm not sure where we're going to seat you...
我得喝一杯
I need a drink.
笑毛笑啊你?
Why are you laughing?
哇 Amy姨好怪咖喔
Wow, Aunt Amy's really weird.
Brian和Erin的婚礼不会下雨吧 千万不能啊
Oh, it can't rain on Brian and Erin's wedding. It just can't!
那也太悲剧了 我可受不了
That would be so awful. I couldn't stand it!
恰恰相反 雨是古代多子多孙的象征
On the contrary. Rain is an ancient symbol of fertility.
每对新人都该这么幸运
Every couple should be so lucky.
这还不知道嘛
Oh, don't you see?
一点小雨才不会破坏Brian和Erin的大喜日子呢
A little rain won't spoil the happiest day of Brian and Erin's life.
外面或许是在下雨 可这里却是暖阳普照
It may rain out there, but in here the sun will be shinning
现在正式下身地狱
We are now entering hell.
请确保胳膊和手肘不要伸出车窗外
Please keep your hands and elbows inside the car.
你们就是Erin表妹吧
You must be Erin's cousin.
我是 但Daira 她表妹那个...
I am. But Daria's, um, her cousin...
啥?
What?
没什么
Nevermind.
是这样 我其实是受保护的证人
Actually, I'm in the witness protection program.
Morgendorffer一家善良地收养了我
The Morgendorffers were kind enough to take me in
因为我的亲生父母被暴徒残杀了
after my real family was exterminated by the mob.
好吧 你怎么没和我们穿同一款伴娘服啊?
Well, how come you didn't get the same dress as the rest of us?
穿了
I did.
话说回来 错过彩排晚宴真是你们的遗憾
Anyway, it's too bad you guys missed the rehearsal dinner.
超级好玩
It was so fun.
我带你们去见护花使者吧
Let me introduce you to your escorts.
Daria Quinn 这位是Garrett
Daria, Quinn, this is Garrett.
Garrett跟Quinn一对
Garrett will be with Quinn.
太好了
Of course.
Quinn 你真是我见过最萌人的小家伙儿
Quinn, you're just about the loveliest thing I ever saw.
谢谢
Thanks.
你能不能帮我去拿杯汽水
Do you think you could get me some soda
只要那么一小小片的柠檬 谢谢啦
with just an eentsy-weentsy slice of lemon, please?
Daria 这位是你男伴 Luhrman
Daria, this is your escort, Luhrman.
太好了
Of course.
你好啊 Daryea
How do you do, Da-rye-a.
是Daria 好吧
It's Daria, actually.
抱歉
Sorry.
那个 Luhrman 是你的名还是你的姓?
So, Luhrman. Is that your first name or your last name?
很重要吗?
Does it matter?
他俩貌似很投机诶
Well, they seem to be hitting it off.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
她狂野 她泼辣 她可人
She's rough, she's tough, she's lovely.
身着贝弗利山哈维斯出品真丝牛皮礼服的Sandi
Our Sandi is in a silk and rawhide outfit by Harve's of Beverly Hills,
表现出人生最欢乐的时光并不一定灰暗无光
proving that the happiest day of your life doesn't have to be dull.
举起手来 汉子们
Stick 'em up, hombres.
下面是身着雷柏出品顺滑绸缎礼服的俏妞Brittany
Here's lovely Brittany in a sleeky and satiny number from Laburb
好像在说
that says,
今天也许并非人家婚礼 去他的 我就是要跳舞
this may be my wedding day but, dammit, I wanna dance!
醒醒 Brittany上台了
Wake up! It's Brittany!
啥? 诶 我去啊
What? Huh? Oh, man!
貌似你让咱俩暴露了
I think you're blowing our cover.
Kevin 你来这儿干嘛啊?
Kevin, what are you doing here?
惊喜呀 宝贝
Surprise, babe!
值此分享...
And as we share...
这对年轻新人Brian和Eric喜结连理之时
the joy of this lovely young couple, Brian and Erin,
我们不得不追寻 爱是什么?
we are compelled to ask, what is love?
是的 爱 就像源自高山的一条小溪
Yes, love, like a tiny rivulet which begins in a high mountain,
唯有历经千万英里的曲折蜿蜒
and only after twisting and turning for thousands of miles,
克服无计其数的障碍
overcoming uncountable obstacles,
最终得以相汇 合流
must eventually meet, and merge,
融汇成广阔的爱情海
with that great ocean of love
是与生俱来 也是命中注定
which is its birthright and its destiny.
是她
It was her.
宝贝 都说抱歉了嘛
Babe, I said I was sorry.
要是现场有个超级星探怎么办?
What if there had been someone there from a major talent agency?
怎么赔?
What then?
那... 我猜他们已经见识到你的天赋了
Well, I guess they would've seen that you're talented.
全都是你猜的 不是吗?
Oh, that's what you guess, is it?
更有可能人家猜到我跟混球之王谈恋爱
More like they would guess I'm dating the king of the jerks,
人家猜对了
and they'd be right!
快看看这些美丽的花喔
Wow! Look at all these flowers.
是用来卖的还是用来摆的?
Are these for sale or just display?
他们就跟我说
So they said to me,
"我们就选你当副总裁
"Why don't we just make you VP
掌管公司整体运作吧"
and have you take over the whole damn operation?"
当时我刚刚29岁
And here I was, 29 years old.
是 你说过了 话说你跟Rita咋认识的?
Yeah, you mentioned. So, how'd you meet Rita?
你知道的 我们都喜欢大海 我有艘帆船
Well, you know, we both love the sea. I have a sailboat.
她又有点呆
And she's a little dingy!
我开玩笑 别介意
I'm kidding, of course.
认了也无妨
Well, let's face it.
Rita是有点轻浮 不过她可是床上猛虎
Rita's a little flighty, but she's a tiger in the bed.
继续满
Keep going.
好吧 感觉她们家都有这病史
Yeah, well, I guess it runs in the family.
你刚才说什么?
What did you say?
只是无关紧要的叨逼叨 没什么
Just a little pointless chit chat. Forget it.
你要再来杯汽水吗?
Would you like another soda?
不用了
No, uh...
要不然咱俩分一瓶下水道清洗剂喝?
Or shall we just split a bottle of drain cleaner?
搞清楚我的话只是开玩笑好吧
Please be assured that my remark was intended in jest,
不是要煽动任何形式的自残行为
and not as an incitement to any type of self-destructive behavior.
你不是本地人吧 对吗?
You're not from around here, are you?
Daria 你在这啊
Daria, there you are!
真不敢相信我在婚礼前都没能见到你
I can't believe I didn't get to see you before the wedding!
婚礼办得特别好
It was a lovely ceremony.
你还没见过Brian吧 是不是超帅的?
Oh, but you haven't met Brian. Isn't he marvelous?
他在政府机关工作 搞情报的
He works for the government. Intelligence.
Erin
Erin!
知道啦 知道啦 我什么都不该说的
I know, I know, I'm not supposed to say anything,
可就是厉害嘛
but isn't it exciting?
要是国家机密遭遇泄露
If our national security is compromised,
追根究底肯定有个女人在作祟
you can bet there's a woman at the bottom of it.
真是的
Oh, you.
老天啊
Oh, God.
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria,
你怎么没穿其他伴娘的那款礼服?
how come you're not wearing the same dress as everybody else?
穿了 我要去一下...
I am. I think I'll go to the...
小妞屋?
The little girl's room?
是 小妞屋
Yeah, the little girl's room.
我去给鼻子打点粉 看下丝袜的破洞有没有变大
I'm going to powder my nose and check the seams on my nylons.
抱歉 你刚说你是做什么的?
I'm sorry, what did you say you do?
我貌似听到搞情报的 但绝壁不可能
I thought I heard intelligence, but that can't be right.
波涛汹涌 狂野的爱情之海
A wild, rolling, surging ocean of love,
作为身只影单的个体 我们没办法掌控
on which we, as mere individuals, have no control.
你明白我所说的话吗?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
不太明白
I'm not sure.
嗨 Quinn 嗨 神父
Hi, Quinn. Hi, Father.
其实我是个牧师 不是神父
Actually, I'm a minister, not a priest.
重要的是
The important thing is,
你是这个社区传颂美德的发声筒
you're the voice of morality in the community.
我恨穿正式礼服的自己 恨穿它的所有人
I hate myself in a formal dress, and everyone else, too.
你对这一套也不怎么感冒
You don't look too thrilled about things, either.
不 我为这场盛大的家庭宴会狂喜过头了
Oh, no. I'm overjoyed to be at this big family event.
每天的生活已经够辱人不倦了
Day to day life isn't humiliating enough.
话说 你现在差不多上大学了吧
Let's see, you're in college now, or something.
非常不幸 还在高中
Still high school, unfortunately.
我对高中生活还有点模糊的记忆
I have some vague memories of high school,
不过现在 你们都随身带枪的 对吧?
but these days, you all carry weapons, right?
像这种正式场合就不必了
Well, not to formal occasions like this.
这是你们这些小孩的失手之处
That's where you kids make your mistake.
我是说
I mean...
爱汝之友邻 爱汝之手足 爱汝之双亲
Love thy neighbors, love thy brother, love thy parents.
每翻开新的一页 就去爱 爱 爱
Every time you turn a page, love, love, love.
我还以为人过三十
I thought when I hit thirty
就不会再在这种家庭活动上不得其所了
I would stop feeling out of place with these family things.
你觉得不得其所?
You feel out of place?
你没发现我那俩姐们儿忙着互相攀比
You didn't notice my sisters are so busy competing with each other
我都进不了他们的雷达区么?
that I don't even register on their radar?
是 可我还以为你都不在乎了呢
Yeah, but I just figured you were above all that.
我是说 你蛮...
I mean, you're kind of...
酷?
Cool?
我知道你没法对我说出口
I know, you can't say that to me.
少年之约嘛
Law of the teenagers.
谢谢你的尊重
Thank you for respecting it.
小时候 Helen和Rita一天到晚争风吃醋
When I was a kid, with Helen and Rita going at it all the time,
留下我一个人 就去做了体育解说员
all they left for me to do was to supply the color commentary.
后来某天
Then, one day,
我发现我带着自己的一套世界观长大了
I found myself all grown up with my own point of view,
感到没有什么义务
and feeling no particular obligation
要听任何人扯淡 一直如此
to listen to anyone else's B.S. Ever.
看来这套世界观效力蛮大的
So it actually worked out pretty well.
除了我得来婚礼见我姐们儿 是很强大
Unless I have to see my sisters at a wedding, yeah.
神吐槽 一招吃遍天下
Sarcasm. It's a great way to deal.
不过这事你半点都不知道的 对吧?
But, you wouldn't know anything about that, would you?
嘿 怎么了嘛?
Hey, what's the matter?
这件事开始让我苦恼了
This whole thing is starting to get to me.
我是说 Daria有道理
I mean, Daria had a point.
为什么高中生得想着"我要结婚"呢?
Why should high school kids be thinking about marriage?
要是再看见可人女孩跟无脑笨蛋在一起...
If I see one more sweet, dopey girl stuck with a lame-brain idiot...
都不在啦啦队吗?
Not even the pep squad?
不在啦啦队
Not even the pep squad.
跟你老实说吧 Daphne 我根本没时间
I'll be honest with you, Daphne: I just can't find the time.
怎么会?
How come?
这个... 首先我得工作
Well, first of all, there's my work.
你做什么的?
What do you do?
我是脱衣舞女
I'm an exotic dancer.
在俱乐部那种
You know, at a club.
我会脱光衣服在陌生男人面前跳舞
I take my clothes off and dance for strange men.
真的?
Really?
这妹子真有一套
She's really very good.
你见过她?
You've seen her?
我要去找一下Quinn
I'd better go check on Quinn.
不敢想象她现在忙活啥呢
I can't imagine what's keeping her.
不过真是一场不错的婚礼 不是吗?
Oh, it was a lovely ceremony, though, wasn't it?
是的呢 Rita
It really was, Rita.
就是可惜老妈不能过来
I'm just so sorry Mom couldn't be here.
这个不用担心 账单一寄到 她自会感同身受的
Don't worry, she'll get to live it all vicariously when the bills arrive.
Jake 再帮我拿杯酒过来好吗?
Jake, how about getting me another glass of wine?
天啊 亲爱的 还是不要...
Gee honey, maybe you shouldn't...
Jake 赶紧给我拿杯酒过来
Jake, I'd really like an other glass of wine, now.
好嘞
Right.
Helen 你不是在挖苦我吧
Helen, you're not bitter about this.
Rita 拜托 我挖苦你干嘛啦?
Rita, please. Why would I be bitter?
你和Erin就该得到最好的 你们一直是
You and Erin deserve the best. You always have.
才不是 我该被永世惩罚
Oh, no I should be punished forever
因为我做了一些错误决定
because I made a few bad decisions.
嗨 你俩现在又在呛什么呢?
Hi. What are you two arguing about now?
呛? 我俩才没呛架呢
Arguing? We're not arguing.
还在生气爸给Rita买了豪爵
Still mad because Dad gave Rita that MG
却只给你买了普利茅斯·勇士?
and all you got was a Plymouth Valiant?
天啊 Amy 你真是什么都记得
My goodness, Amy, the things you remember.
那款是道奇·达特
It was a Dodge Dart.
我想我要说的是 Quinn
I guess what I'm trying to say, Quinn, is,
我可能是个教士 但我也是个男人啊
I may be a man of the cloth, but I'm also a man.
Quinn 你在这啊 神父...
Quinn, there you are. Father...
其实我是牧师 不是神父
Actually, I'm a minister, not a priest.
我们都在问你去哪了呢
We've all been wondering where you were.
真的?
Really?
反正我是的
Well, I know I have.
我刚在跟Quinn解释
I've just been explaining to Quinn
对于你们这样的年轻人 感情是多么的困惑
how emotions can be confusing for young people like yourselves.
恕我直言 神父
With all due respect, Father,
恐怕你不属于怀有这种困惑情感的年轻人之列
I wonder if maybe you're not the one with the confusing emotions.
我不知道你是什么意思
I'm not sure I take your meaning.
我想你懂的
Oh, I think you do.
不要嘛
Oh, no.
所以呢 原来只要稍加训练
So, it turns out that you could go through training and
要上空间站工作 只是不出三个月的事罢了
be up there working on the space station in under three months.
现在我在等我的太空饮料
Now I'm just waiting for my Tang.
你说的是真的?
Wow. Is that true?
不是真的 全是我瞎编的
No, it's not true. I just made it up.
还有 我不是脱衣舞女 不懂海豹突击队
Also, I'm not an exotic dancer, I don't know Seal,
也没被深海鱼怪诱拐过
and I wasn't abducted by the undersea fish people.
我们觉得还是不要再跟你说话了
We decided we'd better not talk to you anymore.
什么?
What?
不是我们不喜欢你啦 只是...
It's not that we don't like you. It's just...
你有点问题耶
You have problems.
是啊
Well, duh.
亲爱的 你看咱们是不是该回去了
Honey, maybe we ought to think about getting back.
不要 我的小派对刚开始 服务生
No, my little party's just beginning. Waiter!
来吧 我给你拿点咖啡和婚礼蛋糕来
Here, I'll get you some coffee and wedding cake.
Rita肯定爱死那一幕
Oh, Rita would love that,
亲眼看我在她面前长脂肪
seeing me balloon up right in front of her.
Helen 你说话声音有点大耶
Helen, um, you're being kind of loud.
才没 你不会想当众吵架吧 啊?
Oh, no! We don't want a scene, do we?
我们不会要破坏这好好的婚礼吧
We don't want to spoil the lovely wedding that
好好老妈可花了好好一笔银子呢 好不好?
lovely Mother spent so much lovely money on, do we.
两位没什么事吧?
Is everything okay here?
有件事你说得倒是没错
Well, you were right about one thing:
某人确实选郎有方
she sure knows how to pick 'em!
- 嘿 听着 - 快别说了
- Hey, look! - Keep it down!
你敢教训我?
Wanna make me?
发生什么了 Helen?
What's going on? Helen?
你怎么会不知道发生了什么 老妈
Oh, you know perfectly well what's going on, Mother.
你这个悲剧男友想当众干架
Your pathetic boyfriend is making a scene!
你说悲剧是什么意思?
What do you mean pathetic?
照镜子就知道 伙计
Look in the mirror, pal!
我只有一件事要说 Rita
I just want to say one thing, Rita.
你可能是漂亮的那个 可能是老妈宠着的那个
You may be the pretty one, you may be the one Mom loves,
但我特么会自力更生
but I worked my damn butt off!
Helen姨 够啦
Aunt Helen! Please!
发生什么了? 不要拌鸡嘴 女士们
What's going on? No cat fights, ladies!
闭上嘴吧 你个史前低能儿
Shut the hell up, you prehistoric imbecile!
情况越来越出位了
Things are getting ugly.
我们可以来个草率又不经意的露脸
I suggest we make a hasty but unobtrusive exit.
真的?
Really?
走起 我们去找哪里有芝士薯条
Let's go find a place that serves cheese fries.
你吃 我看着
You eat, I'll watch.
我要离开一下
I'm, uh, taking off.
好 留我在这看这帮疯狗
Oh, sure, leave me to the dogs.
想来就一起走咯
You can come if you want.
算了 我想坐在这儿 看大屠杀怎么发展
No, I prefer to sit here and watch the carnage unfold.
和你相处很愉快
It's been fun, though.
好了啦 我也吃
Oh, all right, I'll eat, too.
跟我来 不要左顾右盼
Follow me. Don't look to the right or left.
你现在对这些人爱莫能助
There's nothing you can do for these people now.
利威尔保龄球馆
这地方应该会有
This place oughta do.
Amy姨
Aunt Amy?
叫Amy吧
Just Amy.
Amy 人生一直这么庸俗白痴 辱人不倦
Amy, is life always tawdry, stupid, and humiliating,
还是只是阶段?
or is it just a phase?
阶段而已
Just a phase.
我现在就盼着随时跳出这个阶段
I'm expecting to grow out of it anytime now.
危险解除
Coast is clear!
一夫三妻对这种猛烈的哺乳动物根本不是事儿
One three-time hubby is not enough for this red hot mammal.
稍后《呕心小世界》带来: 一夫多妻的河马酱
The polygamous hippopotamus, when Sick, Sad World returns.
我不会回去的 甭管是谁派你们来的
I'm not going back there. I don't care who sent you.
你觉得这货眼熟么?
Does he look familiar to you?
摇滚乐队Ugly Kid Joe首张专辑
我貌似在《美国衰仔》里见过他
I think I saw him on America's Least Wanted.
估计你会想问我
I suppose you want to ask me
你妈妈小时候是什么样的
what your mother was like as a child.
好呗 什么样的?
Okay. What was she?
超级无敌眼中钉
A tightly wound pain in the ass.
换话题?
New topic?
你说咯
Name it.
我... 我都不知道发生了什么
I don't... I don't know what happened.
我一张嘴和他说话 他就...
One minute I had him, and then...
这里一切尽在掌控 长官们
Everything's under control here, officers.
二位何不去买杯咖啡什么的 算我的
Why don't you two go have a cup of coffee or something, on me.
别担心 我是受伤常客
Don't worry, I'm no stranger to pain.
我爱你 Helen
I love you, Helen!
我也爱你啊
I love you, too!
先生 白天的时候来玩会不会更有趣呢?
Sir, wouldn't this be more enjoyable in the daytime?
带几个小伙伴什么的?
Perhaps with some partners?
闭嘴 小子 搞得灯光都晃悠了
Don't talk, son. You're shaking the light.
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组